The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
The suction force here is incomparably stronger.
Resisting it with brute force
is definitely not the way to escape.
To break out of this situation,
I must make this force my own.
11 years later
My Dao of the Underworld has 2 parts.
The first one is the Underworld River.
The second one is condensing the river's soul.
I've been sitting here for 11 years,
trapped by this suction force.
But the power of this abyss
is an opportunity...
to breakthrough !
The principles of the heavens and the earth
lie within the flow of energy.
I am the power
of the Underworld !
Power of the Underworld
Dao of the Underworld 3rd part
Go down...
I beg you !
Take me down !
I beg you...
I just want
to take a look...
The All-Seer and company are about to arrive.
I don't have time for this.
I can't help you.
If you want to leave,
then go.
You...
Don't you want to know the true history
of the bead in your soul ?
Don't you
want that woman's broken soul to revive ?
What did you say !?
I can tell you the origin of that bead
and the method to resurrect the broken soul.
I can even
give you the opportunity to leave this place.
I don't know if what she said is true.
But...
a glimmer of hope
is enough.
Rest assured,
I am not deceiving you.
I'm also making a big decision
by telling you all this.
This is...
Allheaven
Star System
My homeland,
the Allheaven Star System.
Now that we're here,
it's your turn.
Home...
A long time ago,
there was a sacred cultivation ground beneath the starry sky
called the Celestial Domain.
Legend says it abandoned the cultivators
leaving behind only 4 gates of ascension.
Wind,
Rain,
Thunder,
and Lightning.
The 4 gates later transformed into the Celestial Realms.
The 4 Celestial Realms govern the 4 Star Systems.
Above our Allheaven Star System
lies the Thunder Celestial Realm.
The Heaven Defying Bead
first appeared in our Allheaven Star System.
When it appeared,
all the top cultivators sensed the aura of the Ancient Celestial Domain
and went crazy for it.
But in the end, it vanished mysteriously.
Countless years later,
for some unknown reason,
it appeared in the Rain Celestial Realm of the Alliance Star System.
Was that ancient teleportation formation
set up by you ?
It's not mine,
but it was indeed made by an Allheaven cultivator.
That teleportation formation is defective,
only an Allheaven Stone can activate it.
That was the story of the Heaven Defying Bead.
As for that broken soul, my ancestors can revive it.
You just need to take me through this vortex
to send me back home.
Every word this woman says
is trying to lure me into the Allheaven Star System.
Which sect in the Allheaven Star System do you belong to ?
The Allheaven Star System has no sects,
only cultivation families.
I belong to
the Xiang family on planet Dong Lin.
I'm afraid that
I can't pass this vortex
with my current cultivation.
You have the Heaven Defying Bead
so you will definitely pass !
Really ?
She's too confident.
This woman must be hiding something !
Don't you want to revive her !?
Wang Lin !
She is luring me to Allheaven
so there must be a catch.
She knows too many of my secrets.
This threat
cannot be left alive.
Stop this !
You...
Without me,
the soul inside your bead will never be able to resurrect !
Are you...
going to give it up like this !?
Shut up !
Wang Lin...
Wang Lin !
What are you doing !?
This woman was sealed inside the scroll
with no hope of ever escaping.
However, she absorbed a Tattoo Beast Atlas and started recovering.
Wang Lin !
Seal !
I curse your Dao to be completely eradicated
and your soul to be extinguished !
The Allheaven Star System is probably real.
And the opportunity to revive Wan'er
might be slim
but must still be investigated.
The Xiang family of planet Dong Lin...
The All-Seer is coming,
the Demon Spirit Land is too dangerous now.
Since I have the token,
they can't open the true cave.
When I come back later,
I must explore the true cave.
Before leaving,
I need to settle a few things.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Quite a few losses...
What happened to the beast pack ?
It's a good thing you're clever.
It seems that woman
has a connection with Senior Zhou Yi.
Senior should be safe for now.
Since I'm not restricted by the suction force,
I don't have to leave through the exit.
We'll go through the Water Demon Country.
Are they trying
to keep us here ?
Get in
or stay here.
Note: In the world of the Mosquito Beasts, if they were abandoned by their king, then they could only die, unless a new king appears that is.
Foolish children...
Given the purity of its bloodline,
this beast could've only been tamed as a child.
Otherwise, it wouldn't have ever followed me.
It's all fate.
When I return,
I will break the restrictions here one by one
and explore all the secrets of this true cave.
Until then,
no one shall enter.
Stone Manor
Sky Demon City
Tomorrow, I will report to the Demon Emperor
and recommend you as a Demon General.
You'll be able to enter the Dragon Pool to cultivate.
Although you won't obtain the true inheritance,
it should
benefit you a lot.
Tomorrow,
I will have to call you as Vice Commander-in-Chief.
This position of Vice Commander-in-Chief
is rightfully mine.
If not for that despicable Wang Lin,
what would Mo Lihai be ?
Wang Lin is my Junior Brother.
This person has been missing for years,
he's probably dead by now.
You remember him as your Junior Brother
but he probably doesn't remember his Senior Brother anymore.
But if he isn't dead,
I will definitely kill him !
Is that so ?
Stop this farce,
come out !
Wang Lin !
Bold of you
to storm my residence !
I once promised someone I would take your life.
Today
is the day I fulfill that promise.
Arrogant brat !
An Illusory Yin puppet !?
Be careful of Master.
Hurry, hurry, hurry !
Come !
Stop running !
The Soul Refining Tribe
will be in your hands from now on.
Ancestor,
are you leaving ?
The cultivation methods inside are for the tribe.
Thirteen,
in your hands
is the complete Giant Demon Clan's body cultivation method.
Cultivate it diligently.
Thank you, Master...
Thirteen
will fulfill this mission !
I'm leaving on this journey
and I don't know when I'll return.
Take care.
Farewell,
Ancestor.
Given Master's words,
I'm afraid that
we will never meet again.
Time to leave.
Greed,
come out to greet me !
Fellow cultivators,
after all these years
you're still as charming as ever.
Fellow cultivator Wang,
I sense that Greed is with you !
Hand him over to me immediately !
Look,
after all these years,
the Sword Saint's temper has only grown worse.
The Sword Saint's concern for his disciples
is only natural.
Master !
It was Greed.
He caused the deaths
of all my Junior Brothers.
Little child,
did this old man personally kill anyone ?
Although you didn't personally harm them,
you still trapped us all
inside the purple mist as sacrifices !
This old man trapped you inside
for the cave's token !
Instead of looking for the one who killed your Junior Brothers,
you came looking for me instead ?
Absurd !
You !
Enough !
Where is
the token !?
You might not believe what I'm about to say
but this old man swears by his tens of thousands of years of cultivation.
The token
is not in my hands !
It's Wang Lin of the Heavenly Fate Sect !
He took the token !
Trying to escape ?
They came earlier than expected !
Xixue's aura !
So it was you !
Wang Lin,
you can't escape.
Since the Blood Ancestor found out about Yao Xixue,
he definitely won't let me off the hook.
If I want to prevent him from pursuing me,
I have to muddy the waters.
The cave you've been looking for
is not the third
but the fourth.
Wang Lin,
where is my daughter !?
The fourth cave
does indeed exist.
But he has clearly already occupied it.
If we don't capture him,
then we will never
be able to enter the true cave.
This Wang Lin must have had some fortuitous encounter
to be able to withstand the power of the vortex !
My wife and I once tried to enter it back then.
Although we failed before,
if we join forces now,
we might be able to send someone across the vortex.
Who goes ?
Which one of us can enter
that we can all trust ?
Unless it is...
This person's cultivation is suitable
and enough to deal with Wang Lin.
Each of us will put a restriction on him
to make sure he doesn't escape our grasp.
What do you all think ?
I think this will work.
I doubt he’d dare to act rashly.
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.